<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>humorous on Practically Insignificant</title>
    <link>/tags/humorous/</link>
    <description>Recent content in humorous on Practically Insignificant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/humorous/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Estimating the Unconditional Median with Deep Learning: A Practical Approach Using R and Keras</title>
      <link>/post/2023-12-02-estimating-the-unconditional-median-with-deep-learning-a-practical-approach-using-r-and-keras/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2023-12-02-estimating-the-unconditional-median-with-deep-learning-a-practical-approach-using-r-and-keras/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: This post is an parody in the same genre as How to Burn Money and Computing Power for a Simple Median.
This post was generated using the same code as in the previous post, but with the prompt:
Write a post in the style of Towards Data Science about the following code. Keep in mind that this code is showing how to estimate an unconditional median using a deep learning model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Burn Money and Computing Power for a Simple Median</title>
      <link>/post/2023-12-02-how-to-burn-money-and-computing-power-for-a-simple-median/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2023-12-02-how-to-burn-money-and-computing-power-for-a-simple-median/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: This is a parody post. It was generated by providing my code to GPT-4 with the prompt:
Turn this into a blog post with the title &amp;quot;World&amp;#39;s Most Expensive Way to Compute a Mean or Median&amp;quot; and then asking GPT-4 to make its initial post even more entertaining and sarcastic.
Introduction Today, we dive into the comedic world of absurdly over-engineered solutions for simple problems. Our target? Calculating a mean or median using R and TensorFlow in what might be the most hilariously unnecessary method ever conceived.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
